<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jobSearch>
  <job id="108850" ncat="105" recordCount="1">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-08-08 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>16779</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Staff Accountant]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=108850]]></url>
    <jobId>108850</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>staffaccountant108850</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p    >The <b>Staff Accountant</b> is responsible for assisting in the month-end close and financial reporting process for the Ardent Information Technology department.  Other accounting duties may be assigned by the IT Controller or the AVP, Budget & Planning.    </p>  <p    ><b>Primary Responsibilities:</b>  </p>  <p    ></p><ul><li>              Assist in month-end close process of the Corporate Office and Corporate consolidations. </li><li>              Prepare, review and analyze various journal entries for accuracy and reasonableness. </li><li>              Prepare and distribute monthly intercompany allocations. </li><li>              Reconcile corporate balance sheet accounts and perform analytical reviews of monthly activity. </li><li>              Field questions from the hospitals' accounting personnel and research accounting issues. </li><li>              Assist in the preparation of corporate schedules for annual audit performed by external auditors. </li><li>              Review AP invoices and process through ImageNow. </li><li>              Maintain ImageNow workflow processes for Corporate Office. </li><li>              Maintain AP Vendor Master in Lawson module. </li><li>              Fixed Assets </li><li>              Unclaimed Property </li><li>              Perform other duties and special projects as assigned. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]-->  <p> </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >   </p>  <p    ><b>Knowledge, Skills, and Abilities:</b>  </p>  <p    ></p><ul><li>              Ability to provide accurate and efficient service under the stress of constant deadlines. </li><li>              Knowledge of Generally Accepted Accounting Principles. </li><li>              Ability to work on different projects at one time. </li><li>              Ability to work and interact with departments throughout the Company. </li><li>              Ability to work independently. </li><li>              Exceptional written and verbal skills. </li><li>              Exceptional problem solving abilities. </li><li>              Exceptional organizational skills. </li><li>              Detail oriented. </li><li>              Skill in the use of personal computers an  d related software applications. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]-->  <p> </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>  <p    >  </p>    <p    ><br></p>  <p    ><b> Qualifications: </b>  </p>  <p    ><b>Education and Work Experience:</b>   </p>  <p    ></p><ul><li>             Bachelor's Degree in Accounting or Finance required. </li><li>             2-5 years of accounting experience required; healthcare and corporate office experience preferred. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p>    <p    >   </p>  <p    ><b>Additional Requirements:</b></p><ul><li>      Excel experience - intermediate to advanced</li><li>          Lawson Financial Accounting and ImageNow experience a plus but not required</li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="109124" ncat="103" recordCount="55">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-08-23 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>17070</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[CNO]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=109124]]></url>
    <jobId>109124</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>Yes</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Lovelace Medical Center</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Albuquerque</facility_city>
    <facility_state>NM</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100024</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>cno109124</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p  ><b> Ardent Health Services </b>  is a nationwide provider of hospital and healthcare services which owns and operates 14 hospitals serving three major markets as well as owning physician practice organizations, diagnostic facilities and ambulatory surgery centers. With annual revenues in excess of $2 billion, we are an established organization that is growing.     </p>  <p  > We are currently recruiting for a <b>Chief Nursing Officer (CNO)</b> to join <b>Lovelace Medical Center</b> which is a part of Lovelace Health System in Albuquerque, NM.   Lovelace Medical Center (LMC) is among New Mexico's most widely recognized and respected health care leaders. The Lovelace Medical Center campus includes Lovelace Medical Center and the Heart Hospital of New Mexico at Lovelace Medical Center. Situated in the heart of Albuquerque, LMC exceeds 11,000 admits and 41,000 Emergency Department visits each year. This 318-bed campus  was recently named to Modern Healthcare's Best Places to Work list,    and was recognized by Truven Health Analytics as one of the nation's Top 50 Cardiac Hospitals. In addition, LMC received the 2015 Midas Platinum+ Quality award. Lovelace Health System was also recently recognized as one of the Top 15 Health Systems by Truven Health Analytics. </p>  <p  > We are searching for a CNO who is interested in joining a stable and growing company where you can make a lasting impact. Our new CNO will be a visionary who is inspired by a challenge and will put forth the effort to succeed. We are seeking a dynamic leader that understands the importance of strong employee relations; someone who provides a positive, healthy work environment, and facilitates organizational improvement through creative initiatives. The CNO at LMC must be a true leader in terms of advising and creating strategies of organizational lay out, nursing development and excellence, new cost-effective programs and productivity.     </p>  <p  > The <b>Chief Nursing Officer</b> will be responsible for the operational, financial, clinical and personnel activities of all assigned clinical services.      </p>  <p  > Primary responsibilities include:     </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  >      Directing nursing services for the      facility and working collaboratively with other care providers      to meet patient care needs.     </li>  <li  >      As a member of the executive team, participating      in the development of and implementation of programs and services,      including system-wide collaboration.     </li>  <li  >      Establishing the vision and providing      leadership in the delivery of optimal patient care and in the achievement      of facility initiatives.     </li>  <li  >      Working with the members of the      management, ancillary and care provider team to assure operational      effectiveness, clinical excellence, physician and employee engagement and patient      satisfaction.     </li> </ul>  <p  >     </p>  <p  ><b><i> REQUIREMENTS </i></b>    </p>  <p  ><b> Education: </b>  BSN  and master's degree required (MSN preferred, but will consider candidates with MHA or MBA).     </p>  <p  ><b> Work Experience: </b>   Five (5) years of progressive experience in a hospital administration. A record of performance demonstrating innovative operations management resulting in improved health outcomes, employee engagement and controlled expenses.     </p>  <p  ><b> Additional Requirements: </b>  Strong clinical nursing experience and a minimum of six (6) years of clinical experience in acute care are required. Strong physician and clinical relationship skills are essential. Previous experience in managing multiple areas of clinical and support operations also required.     </p>  <p  >   </p>  <p  >   </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Executive</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="107851" ncat="101" recordCount="56">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-06-08 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>15712</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Inpatient Coder]]></jobTitle>
    <department><![CDATA[Health Information Management]]></department>
    <schedule>Full Time</schedule>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=107851]]></url>
    <jobId>107851</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>inpatientcoder107851</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<h3  > Ardent is looking for Inpatient Coders!  These positions can be located in Nashville TN, Tulsa OK, Albuquerque NM or Amarillo, TX. There are are also opportunities for remote Coders!  </h3><p> <b>Ardent Health Services:</b> </p><ul  ><li>  3 health systems with 14 hospitals  </li><li  > 2,194 licensed beds </li><li  > 12,000 employees </li><li  > 3 physician groups with 270 employed physicians </li></ul><div><p    >  The Inpatient Coder will bring to the table proven experience in all aspects of hospital coding, which includes the technical abilities to perform facility coding for hospital inpatient services. To achieve appropriate and timely reimbursement and data integrity the IP Coder must ensure accurate and compliant application of correct coding principles for hospital services. and participate in any coding-related projects.    </p><p    > The IP Coder is responsible for </p><p    ></p><ul><li> Assigning ICD-9-CM and/or ICD-10 diagnosis and procedure codes and present on admission (POA) indicators; HCPCS/CPT codes; and modifiers. </li><li> Maintains at least a 97% accuracy rate. </li><li> Maintains average to high productivity based on Ardent Shared Coding Productivity Standards. </li><li> Abstracting of facility required data in McKesson Star. </li><li> Working applicable McKesson Pre-Bill Edits and Receivable Work Station (RWS) requests. </li><li> Follow up on missing documentation, including the generation of appropriate queries, as needed. </li><li> Communication of issues to the MS-DRG, APC Manager and/or Director Shared Coding Services, as appropriate. </li><li> Thorough understanding of ICD-9-CM/ICD-10 Official Coding Guidelines for Coding and Reporting and <i>AHA Coding Clinic.</i> </li><li> Thorough understanding of HCPCS/CPT coding systems and <i>CPT Assistant</i> and <i>Coding Clinic for HCPCS </i>guidelines. </li><li> Thorough understanding of Medicare Inpatient Prospective Payment System (IPPS), Medicare Severity-Diagnosis Related Groups (MS-DRGs). </li><li> Thorough understanding of Medicare Outpatient Prospective Payment System (OPPS), Ambulatory Payment Classification (APC). </li><li> Understanding of coding resources and tools, including 3M 360 Encompass. </li><li> Acknowledgement of receipt and review of updated Ardent coding policies. </li><li> Maintains continuing education (CE) requirements per Ardent policy. </li></ul><p>   </p><p    > <b>       Education </b> :       </p><div>  <p    ></p><ul><li> Successful completion of a Medical Terminology, Anatomy and Physiology, and Pharmacology course </li><li> Successful completion of an ICD-9-CM and HCPCS/CPT coding class </li><li> Coding/HIM certification </li></ul> <b> Experience & Requirements </b>: <p>   </p>  <p    ></p><ul><li> 3 years coding/abstracting experience in hospital inpatient and outpatient coding.  Advanced training in ICD-10-CM and PCS. </li><li> Coding credential though AHIMA or AAPC. </li><li> Computer and software skills, including Word, Excel, PowerPoint, encoder/grouper </li><li> Strong written and verbal communications skills </li><li> Organizational skills </li><li> Leadership skills </li></ul><p>   </p>          </div><p    >                                </p></div>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="108008" ncat="103" recordCount="120">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-08-16 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>15873</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Director, Clinical Systems]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=108008]]></url>
    <jobId>108008</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>directorclinicalsystems108008</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p  > The <b>Director, Clinical Systems</b> provides leadership and strategic direction in the functional support, design, instruction and guidance of the clinical applications to enable the achievement of success in the business operation at the division office and hospital facilities. Responsibilities include:  providing leadership to the Clinical Applications Team, developing system strategies that are congruent with overall IT strategies as well as the business goals of stakeholders, fiscal and HR accountability for the Clinical Team, conducting business needs analysis, identifying and mitigating IT risks, managing the implementation of clinical application projects </p><p  >   </p><p  > <b>Primary Duties and Responsibilities</b>   </p><p  ><b>     </b></p><p  ><b> Analysis and Solution Definition   </b></p><p    ></p><ul><li>              Quickly understands the business issues and data challenges of the organization and industry. </li><li>              Identifies the organization's strengths and weaknesses and suggests areas of improvement. </li><li>              Develops functional requirements, specifications and system design specifications for business requests. </li><li>              Develops or oversees the development of system documentation, user manuals and training classes for  application suite. </li><li>              Creates and maintains detailed test plans and scripts. </li><li>              Leads testing efforts and ensures issues are identified, tracked, reported on and resolved in a timely manner. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p  >       </p><p  >  <b>Project Execution</b>    </p><p    ></p><ul><li>              Evaluates current state processes and identifies gaps to future state process around utilization of applications to maximize departmental and organizational efficiency and effectiveness. </li><li>              Communicates and applies project standards. </li><li>              Enforces of project deadlines and schedules. </li><li>              Takes input from supervisor and appropriately and accurately applies comments/feedback. </li><li>              Manages resources in accordance with project schedule. </li><li>              Consistently delivers high-quality services to business stakeholders. </li><li>              Understands the components of running a fiscally successful project and department. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p  ><b>     </b></p><p  ><b> Communication   </b></p><p    ></p><ul><li>              Assists in the facilitation of team and client meetings. </li><li>              Delivers informative, well-organized presentations. </li><li>              Understands how to communicate difficult/sensitive information tactfully. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p  >   </p><p  ><b> Problem Solving   </b></p><p    ></p><ul><li>              Prioritizes and resolves issues. </li><li>              Exhibits confidence and an extensive knowledge of emerging industry practices when solving business problems. </li><li>              Collaborates with business stakeholders to introduce innovative solutions. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p  >   </p><p  ><b> Leadership   </b></p><p    ></p><ul><li>              Generates enthusiasm among team members. </li><li>              Challenges others to develop as leaders while serving as a role model. </li><li>              Facilitates effective team interaction. </li><li>              Acknowledges and appreciates each team member's contributions. </li><li>              Develops and fosters relationships with business stakeholders. </li><li>              Continually seeks opportunities to increase customer satisfaction. </li><li>              Manages business stakeholder expectations effectively. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p  ><b> <br clear="all"> General </b></p><p    ></p><ul><li>              Participates in leadership incident manager on-call rotation. </li><li>              Ability to travel up to 50%. </li><li>              Embodies and Promotes Core Values:  Inquisitiveness, Team-Mindedness, Passionate, and Positive Attitude. </li><li>              Other duties as assigned. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p  ><b> Qualifications   </b></p><p  ><b>     </b></p><p  ><b> Education   </b></p><p    ></p><ul><li>              Bachelor's Degree (Equivalent business experience will be considered) </li><li>              Master's Degree preferred </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p    ><b>   </b></p><p  ><b> Leadership and Experience </b></p><p  > </p><ul   type="circle"> <li> Five or more  years of management/leadership experience required </li><li  > Five years of experience in clinical care or healthcare delivery with EPIC application experience preferred </li>  <li  > Subject matter expertise in multiple      clinical application modules/solutions with experience in configurations      and system setup   </li>  <li  > Proven ability to understand business      and clinical issues and objectives as well as the ability to translate them      into application solutions and workflow   </li>  <li  > Established project manager of multiple      large scale large projects of 12+ team members, with experience managing:   </li>  <li  > Resources and critical path   </li>  <li  > Project scope   </li>  <li  > Issues identification and oversight   </li>  <li  > Change control processes   </li>  <li  > Stakeholder communications   </li>  <li  > Project budget   </li>  <li  > Excellent communication skills   </li>  <li  > Preferred experience with the following      EPIC Clinical or Ancillary Products </li></ul>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="107853" ncat="104" recordCount="133">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-06-08 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>15716</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Case Management Auditor/Educator]]></jobTitle>
    <department><![CDATA[Revenue Cycle]]></department>
    <schedule>Full Time</schedule>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=107853]]></url>
    <jobId>107853</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>casemanagementauditoreducator107853</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p><b> This position can be located in Tulsa, OK - Albuquerque, NM or Amarillo, TX!  </b></p><p> Ardent Health Services invests in quality health care. In people, technology, facilities and communities, Ardent makes considerable investments, producing high quality care and extraordinary results.  </p><h3  > Ardent includes: </h3><ul  ><li  > 3 health systems with 14 hospitals </li><li  > 2,194 licensed beds </li><li  > 12,000 employees </li><li  > 3 physician groups with 270 employed physicians </li></ul><p    > Reporting to the AVP of Case Management, the Case Management Auditor/Educator shall perform reviews for Case Management process improvement to include review of case management documentation, case management processes, utilization review processes and documentation, assisting with education for case management staff at all ardent facilities as needed, observation and 1-2 day inpatient audits, and transitions of care evaluation and process improvements.  The CM Auditor/Educator will assist in the development of the processes to standardize Case Management, Transitions of Care, and Utilization Review. </p><p    > <b><i>Education: </i></b>Prefer<b><i> </i></b>a Bachelor's Degree in Nursing or Licensed Master Level Social Worker with Case Management certification required (ACM or CCM).     </p>  <p    ><b><i>   </i></b></p>  <p    > <b><i>Work Experience:</i></b>  A minimum of four years of experience as an RN Case Manager, Utilization Review RN or LMSW Case Manager. An ACM or CCM certification is required for the position or must be obtained in 1 year. Experience auditing and reviewing medical records preferred. Completion of reports for documentation of issues in Word and Excel spreadsheet formats. Proficiency with Power Point a plus. Conduct medical chart and process reviews for potential opportunities to improve Case Management, TOC and UR system-wide.  </p>  <p    >       Skills need to include knowledge of hospital operations, hospital department case management, TOC, and utilization review, revenue cycle services and CMS regulations.  Extensive knowledge of all CMS regulations regarding Conditions of Participation for Discharge Planning, OPPS and IPPS documentation regulations, Two-Midnight Rule, CMS Inpatient only list, NOTICE Act.    </p>  <p    >     </p>  <p    >    </p><p    > <b  ><i>Additional Requirements:</i></b>  Communication skills and developing a rapport with hospital administration, department managers, and case management staff are paramount to identifying issues and developing resolution. Must be detail oriented and work both independently and collaboratively with various administrative and clinical staff.      Requires willingness and ability to travel up to 50% or greater.  </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 1.      Reviews case management documentation and processes, UR processes and documentation and TOC    processes and documentation to ensure efficiency and effectiveness.  This includes:   </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]-->            <!--[endif]-->Improvement of facility processes and procedures to assure timely and accurate CM/TOC/UR processes.    </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]-->            <!--[endif]-->Development and implementation of System-wide Denial Management for regulatory payors.    </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]-->            <!--[endif]-->Develop clinical in-services and education programs for field staff and establish procedures for timely and accurate for CM/TOC/UR delivery.   </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]-->            <!--[endif]-->Develop and maintain collaborative working relationship with all Ardent facilities including CM/TOC/UR, Administration and all other departments that impact Case Management processes.    </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 2.        <!--[endif]-->Inter-relate with department managers to identify trends and issues.  Assist in directing resolution of the issue.   </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]-->            <!--[endif]-->Document identified issues using current tools or develops new tools to enhance process.   </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]-->            <!--[endif]-->Monitor identified issues and the timeline for resolution.   </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]-->            <!--[endif]-->Document financial impact of identified issue.   </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 4.        <!--[endif]-->Address revenue cycle QA issues as needed.   </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 5.        <!--[endif]-->Monitor and trend CM/TOC/UR processes to identify opportunities for process improvement.   </p><p  ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 6.        <!--[endif]-->Function as a resource to the CM/TOC/UR departments and Facility Administration.     </p><p    > 7.      Complies, reconciles and distributes reports timely to the appropriate personnel.                         </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="108841" ncat="105" recordCount="151">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-08-08 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>16778</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Financial Analyst]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=108841]]></url>
    <jobId>108841</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>financialanalyst108841</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p class=""> Reporting to the Controller of Ardent's Information Technology Department, the <b>Financial Analyst</b> is responsible for conducting financial analysis projects and statistical studies. You will perform a variety of complicated tasks, including financial modeling, projections, monitoring, and tracking. </p><p class=""> </p><p class=""> <b>Primary Responsibilities:</b>   </p><p  ></p><ul><li> Month-end  Review RNI, Accruals and Prepaid schedules.  </li><li> Financial Analysis: </li><li>Review actual in contracts file and labor analysis for accuracy</li><li>Update contract and contract labor projections</li><li>Coordinate and obtain monthly cost trackers for strategic and capital projects</li><li> Epic - Tracking and updating the financials for Ardent's roll out of Epic. </li><li> PO's / Invoices  Provide input on coding questions for Pos and Invoices </li><li> Capital Forecasting / Budgeting  </li><li> Provide direct input for project owners to prepare CER's </li><li> Validation of cost offsets within the CER documentation </li><li> Prepare initial forecast schedule using monthly cost trackers for Controller review. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p class="">   </p><p class=""> <b> Knowledge, Skills, and Abilities:</b>   </p><p  ></p><ul><li> Ability to provide accurate and efficient service under the stress of constant deadlines. </li><li> Knowledge of Generally Accepted Accounting Principles. </li><li> Ability to work on different projects at one time. </li><li> Ability to work and interact with departments throughout the Company. </li><li> Ability to work independently. </li><li> Exceptional written and verbal skills. </li><li> Exceptional problem solving abilities. </li><li> Exceptional organizational skills. </li><li> Detail oriented. </li><li> Skill in the use of personal computers and related software applications. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p class=""><br></p><p class=""> <b>Qualifications:</b> </p><p class=""> </p><p class=""> <b>Education:</b>    </p><p  ></p><ul><li> Requires a Bachelor's degree </li><li> CPA preferred </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p class=""> <b>Work Experience: </b>   </p><p  ></p><ul><li> 3+ years of experience in Accounting. </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p class=""> <b>Other Factors:   </b>   </p><p  ></p><ul><li> Healthcare experience strongly preferred. </li><li> Must be familiar with standard concepts, practices, and procedures. </li><li> Should possess experience and judgment to plan and accomplish goals. </li><li> Must have strong financial modeling/projection experience. </li><li> Lawson experience is preferred. </li><li> Hyperion experience is preferred.  </li></ul><!--[if !supportLists]--><p> </p><p class="">     </p><p class="">     </p><p> </p><p class="">   </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="109135" ncat="105" recordCount="177">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-08-23 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>17087</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Sr. Auditor]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=109135]]></url>
    <jobId>109135</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>srauditor109135</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p  > Ardent Health Services (AHS) is a national healthcare company headquartered in Nashville, TN.  Our subsidiaries own and operate hospitals and multispecialty physician practices in three states.  Ardent includes:  3 health systems with 14 hospitals, 2,194 licenses beds, 12,000 employees, and 3 physician groups with 270 employed physicians.  Within the industry, we are noted for recognizing that every hospital is as unique as the community it serves.  This in-depth understanding of how health care works at the local level is one of our great strengths.</p><p  >We are seeking a dynamic, self-motivated <b>Senior Auditor</b> to join our team in Nashville, Tennessee.  In our Audit Services department, you will continue to develop the skills you learned in public accounting that will ultimately lead to your placement in an operations, financial or other role within the Company.</p><p  >As a Senior Auditor, you will be responsible for leading audit engagements, designing the audit approach to address risk and effectively communicating the results of your procedures.  You will consult with management on special assignments, including accounting matters, contract compliance, operational initiatives and/or due diligence. </p><p  >If you are creative, enjoy the pace of public accounting without the hours; have experience using data analysis tools such as Excel, Access or ACL, as well as exceptional financial/operational audit skills, this role will be a perfect fit for you.</p><p  ><b> </b></p><p  ><b>Requirements:  </b></p><p  ><b>Education:  </b></p><p  ></p><ul><li>BS/BA in Accounting, Finance or related field</li><li>Advanced degree preferred</li></ul><p> </p><p  > </p><p  ><b>Experience & Attributes:  </b></p><p  ></p><ul><li>2-3 years of Public Accounting experience preferred</li><li>Certified Public Accountant required</li><li>Healthcare or Health Plan experience preferred</li><li>Efficient use of Excel, Access or ACL</li><li>Demonstrated analytical approach to problem solving</li><li>Ability to lead project activities</li><li>Contribute to strong relationships through interactions with Company management</li><li>Contribute to engagement planning and ensure that products/deliverables address risk</li><li>Strong written and oral communication skills</li><li>Contribute to a positive team attitude</li><li>Willingness to travel up to 25%</li></ul><p> </p><p  >                                                </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="109425" ncat="105" recordCount="179">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-09-07 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>17395</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[IT Help Desk Tech]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=109425]]></url>
    <jobId>109425</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>ithelpdesktech109425</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p  > The  <b> IT Help Desk Tech </b>  is a self-starter with excellent communication skills that include a technical vocabulary.  These individuals provide a helping hand and often progress into other departments within the IT&S team.  You will evaluate user's problems, determine the source, and guide the issue through the proper steps for resolution.     </p>  <p  ><b> Education:  </b>    </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  > High School diploma or equivalent required.       Bachelor's degree preferred.     </li> </ul>  <p  >     </p>  <p  ><b> Experience: </b>       </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  > Two-years experience working with Microsoft      applications (ex. Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint)     </li>  <li  > Successful track record of experience identifying PC      problems to a functional level     </li>  <li  > Successful history of handling repetitive telephone      calls     </li>  <li  > Experience working in a help desk environment     </li>  <li  > Healthcare experience/knowledge a plus     </li>  <li  > Commitment to customer satisfaction     </li> </ul>  <p  ><b> What You'll Do: </b>    </p>  <p  > This dynamic job will present situations that require you think on your feet, but here are a few things you can expect:     </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  >  Assist users with inquires that relate to      department repair policies in a timely manner.     </li>  <li  > Improve the level of Information Service by providing      problem resolution or forwarding inquiries to appropriate      personnel/technician.     </li>  <li  > Analyze types of problems and inquiries to assign      severity levels, assign problem resolution, and follow through on      resolution.     </li>  <li  > Log and input trouble tickets in "Service      Plus" in order to analyze and track service response and problems to      final resolution.     </li>  <li  > Encourage and support a team environment.  Work      with peers to equitably distribute problems and escalations.     </li>  <li  > Stay abreast of the latest technology.  Utilizes      in-house training opportunities to further personal development, as      assigned by Shift Lead.     </li>  <li  > Excellent communication skills both written and verbal.       Easily discuss technology in simple, every day terms.  Highly      organized individual who can manage multiple tasks simultaneously.     </li>  <li  > Conflict resolution and anger diffusion are key      elements to success to gain customer respect and confidence.     </li>  <li  > Ability to work varying shifts to accommodate business      needs.     </li>  <li  > Ability to support twenty-four by seven operations to      include On Call Rotation between Customer Service Representatives.     </li> </ul>  <p    ><b> Benefits: </b>    </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  > Competitive Paid Time Off program     </li>  <li  > 401(k) Retirement Savings     </li>  <li  > Competitive Salary     </li>  <li  > Bonus targets based on company and individual      performance     </li>  <li  > Comprehensive Medical, Dental and Vision Benefits     </li>  <li  > Company provided & Optional Life Insurance     </li>  <li  > Healthcare & dependant care flexible spending      accounts     </li> </ul>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="107356" ncat="103" recordCount="230">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-05-11 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>15164</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Information Security Manager]]></jobTitle>
    <department><![CDATA[It - Information Technology]]></department>
    <schedule>Full Time</schedule>
    <shift>1st - Day</shift>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=107356]]></url>
    <jobId>107356</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>informationsecuritymanager107356</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p>  <b>Ardent Health Services invests in quality health care. In people, technology, facilities and communities, Ardent makes considerable investments, producing high quality care and extraordinary results. We are seeking a leader for the Information Security Team.  </b>  </p><p> Responsible for developing and managing Information Systems security projects including business continuity/disaster recovery, metrics reporting, and regulatory compliance. Oversees IT audits and assessments to ensure corrective action plans are implemented and process improvements maintained. Conducts logical and physical security assessments of networks, systems, and applications. Familiarity with ITGC concepts, practices, and procedures. Relies on extensive experience and judgment to plan and accomplish goals. Leads and directs the work of others. A wide degree of creativity and latitude is expected. Reports to AVP, Information Security.  </p><p    ><b> <u> Education </u> :                     </b></p><p    ><b>  Graduate of accredited university or college in computer-related discipline or equivalent experience in related IT field.      </b></p>  <p    ><b  >  <u>Experience</u>:             </b></p><p> <b  > Minimum of eight years IT experience with at least five in information security or IT auditing. Infrastructure experience including knowledge of Cisco networks, Linux and MS Windows family of operating systems is required.  </b><b  > Prefer   minimum two  years experience in managing complex information technology projects. Strong background in open source security tools is a plus (e.g. Nessus, nmap, OSSIM, Wireshark, etc.).</b>  </p><p    > <b><u> Certificates/ </u></b><b  >  <u>Licenses</u>:                  </b> </p><p    > <b  > CISA and PMP certifications preferred; Recognized IT certifications (CISSP, SSCP) is a plus. </b>  </p><p    ><b> <u> TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE/SKILLS/ABILITIES </u> :    </b></p>  <p    ><b  >  <u>Knowledge</u>:              </b></p><p    ><b  >  Strong knowledge of HIPAA, HITECH, PCI, SOX404, and best practice information security standards (ISO27001/2, NIST 800-series, ITIL, etc.).   Knowledge of computer security issues, requirements, and trends.  Technical knowledge of the software and hardware used within LAN/WAN infrastructure (e.g., Cisco routers & switches, Cisco ASA firewalls, VPN's, patch panels, modems, communication protocols, network nodes, various transmission methodologies and associated network management software). In-depth understanding of TCP/IP (subnetting, services and ports), attack and defense-in-depth strategies, secure network architecture, perimeter security, wireless security, security assessments, incident management, and Linux and Windows operating systems. </b></p>  <p    > <b  > <u>Skills in</u>: </b> </p><p    > <b  > Exception </b><b  > al communication skills  to effectively interact with executive mgmt, IT personnel, business partners, and end users.   </b> </p><p    ><b  >   Strong organization, leadership, and project management skills. Strong analytical and problem solving skills.  </b></p>  <p    > <b> </b><b  ><u>Ability to</u>:</b> </p><p    ><b  > Perform all essential functions. Identify and remediate security vulnerabilities.   </b></p><p    ><b  >  </b><b  > Perform vulnerability analysis, risk analysis, customer training and system technical security reviews and audits.  </b></p><p    ><b  >  </b><b  >Develop, clearly define and document required plans, policies and procedures in support of IT security</b></p><p    > <b  >disaster recovery, and business continuity planning.  </b> </p><p    > <b  >Organize and prioritize work to balance cost and risk factors and bring adequate data security measures to the information technology environments.   </b> </p><p    > <b  >Read and understand related laws and corporate compliance guidance.</b>    </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="108395" ncat="103" recordCount="231">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-07-12 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>16287</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Manager, Charge Integrity]]></jobTitle>
    <department><![CDATA[Finance]]></department>
    <schedule>Full Time</schedule>
    <shift>1st - Day</shift>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=108395]]></url>
    <jobId>108395</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>managerchargeintegrity108395</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p  ><b> This position can be located in Tulsa, Oklahoma - Amarillo, TX or Albuquerque, NM !!  </b></p><p  > The Manager of Charge Integrity has responsibility for the areas set forth in the primary responsibility section.  The Director possesses requisite managerial and technical abilities to provide corporate leadership and direction in maintaining audit protocols, validation of clinical application functionality, processes and work flows for the timely and accurate recording of hospital revenue in regards to charge capture and oversight of the AHS audit team.  This position reports directly to the Director, Charge Integrity and will be responsible for communication from hospital-based leadership as it relates to audit activity, information technology ,Patient Financial Services, and revenue generating departments back to the director for decision making.  This position also has collaborative work relationship with Finance, Health Information/Case Management, and Compliance/Internal Audit. </p>  QUALIFICATIONS      <p    ><b  ><i> Education:  Position requires RN, LPN, and Coding/AHIMA Certification.  Bachelor's Degree in nursing preferred.  </i></b></p>  <p    > <b><i>Work Experience:</i></b>  Minimum of five years of relevant clinical /financial audit experience a must with at least two years of experience in a corporate-based environment specializing in charge capture audits. Must have technical knowledge of correct coding principles of CPT-4/HCPCS/ modifiers assignment, proficient with ICD-10 and DRG assignment knowledge. </p>  <p  > <b><i>Additional Requirements:</i></b>  Proven leadership, management and organizational skills.  Must have a thorough knowledge of hospital operations, hospital department charge capture, charging system, revenue generation, and Medicare regulatory environment.  Must be detail oriented and work both independently and collaboratively with various administrative and clinical areas.  Must have excellent communication skills and understands chain of command with regard to decisions and management of challenges and issues.   </p><p    > <b><i><u>PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES</u></i></b>   </p>  <p  ></p> <ul><li>       Manages the corporate nurse auditors including demonstrated proficiency of coding and required regulations for billing and reporting to all payers.      Uses web-based tools and recommends consulting needs as appropriate. </li><li>       Assists and recommends specific policy development to Director for corporate policies and procedures for audit related activities. </li><li>       Reviews charge integrity workflows to ensure efficiency and effectiveness.      This includes:      Improvement of facility processes and procedures to assure timely and accurate capture of all chargeable activities and develop clinical in-services and education programs for field staff and establish procedures for timely and accurate charge capture mechanisms.      Must be approved by Director of Charge integrity prior to implementation. </li><li>       Ensures accuracy of the audit teams work and provides corrective action when necessary.      </li><li>       May be required to provide input into development of financial impact reports, scorecards, dashboards as it relates to the Charge Integrity departments activity.      Must be able to analyze and articulate findings in all reports, scorecards, etc.    </li><li>       Communicates and listens effectively with internal and external customers; effectively understands and articulates and shares knowledge as appropriate. </li><li>       Assists Director in integration of all new business acquired and within current AHS enterprise.    </li></ul> <p> </p>            <p  > <i>Note:  The essential job functions of this position are not limited to the duties listed above.</i>  </p><p  > Must have a thorough knowledge or gain knowledge quickly of hospital EMR in all AHS markets, hospital operations and department charge capture, charging system, revenue generation, and Medicare regulatory environment.  Must be detail oriented and work both independently and collaboratively with various administrative and clinical areas.  Must have technical knowledge of correct coding principles of CPT-4 /HCPCS /, ICD-10, clinical applications, etc.  </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="109121" ncat="105" recordCount="397">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-08-23 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>17067</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Payroll Manager]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=109121]]></url>
    <jobId>109121</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>payrollmanager109121</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p    >Ardent Health Services (AHS) is a national healthcare company headquartered in Nashville, TN.  Our subsidiaries own and operate hospitals and multispecialty physician practices in three states.  Ardent includes:  3 health systems with 14 hospitals, 2,194 licenses beds, 12,000 employees, and 3 physician groups with 270 employed physicians.  Within the industry, we are noted for recognizing that every hospital is as unique as the community it serves.  This in-depth understanding of how health care works at the local level is one of our great strengths.  </p>  <p    >We have an exciting opportunity to join our team as a <b>Payroll Manager</b>. This dynamic position will have oversight over our corporate payroll department which includes exposure to employees working in multiple states and will be a subject matter expert for payroll throughout our organization.  </p>  <p  >   </p>  <p  ><b>Primary Duties and Responsibilities:  </b></p>  <p    ></p><ul><li>              Maintains production records, timesheets, and payroll system. </li><li>              Responsible for computing withholding and deductions associated with net earnings. </li><li>              Ensures the accurate processing of wage payments to exempt and nonexempt staff including setup and maintenance of direct deposit, W-4 information, garnishments, child support, tax and levies. </li><li>              Transfers payroll labor accounts distribution as appropriate' analyzes, reconciles and balances data processing and electronic time input batches  ensures all systems balance correctly. </li><li>              Interacts with internal and external auditors; provides access to payroll and other related records as required. </li><li>              Maintains records for annual sick worker's compensation audits. </li><li>              Audits and maintains Paid Time Off records for all eligible employees. </li><li>              Compiles and maintains data necessary to calculate and process payments for PTO payoff upon termination. </li><li>              Processes termination documents and final checks. </li><li>              Prepares month-end payroll reconciliation and monthly stats and well as records monthly journal entries based on monthly activity. </li><li>              Responsible for the completion of all year-end reports for all jurisdictions. </li><li>              Assists in the annual budget process as necessary. </li><li>              Answers policy and procedure questions for all levels of employees. </li><li>              Investigates and resolves complex payroll problems according to Labor Code and IRS regulations.     </li><li>              Sorts, prioritizes, reviews for accuracy and process incoming payroll/personnel documents. </li><li>              Provides direction and support to hospital payroll staff related to state and federal laws and regulations as well as the company's policies and procedures. </li><li>              Responsible for filing of monthly, quarterly and year-end local, state and federal tax returns. </li><li>              Verifies employment with outside entities such as banks, etc. </li><li>              Completes calendar year-end processing of payroll, including supplemental payrolls, W-2 and other tax forms. </li></ul><b>Knowledge, Skills, & Abilities:</b><br><ul><li>              Ability to provide accurate and efficient service under the stress of constant deadlines. </li><li>              Knowledge of high-volume, multi-state payroll systems, processes, and procedures. </li><li>              Knowledge of public institution personnel/payroll practices and procedures. </li><li>              Ability to make administrative/procedural decisions and judgments. </li><li>              Knowledge and understanding of payroll documentation procedures and requirements. </li><li>              Skill in the use of personal computers and related software applications. </li><li>              Skill in the use of computer spreadsheet (ie Excel), database, and mainframe applications in a Windows environment. </li><li>              Knowledge of federal and state tax laws. </li><li>              Ability to understand and process complex paperwork. </li><li>              Ability to analyze and solve problems. </li><li>              Knowledge of procedures and standards for check processing. </li><li>              Strong interpersonal and communication skills. </li><li>              Ability to audit and maintain financial records. </li><li>              Ability to understand IRS regulations. </li><li>              Ability to use discretion and ensure confidentiality. </li></ul>                                <p  >   <b>Qualifications</b></p><p  ></p><ul><li> Bachelor's Degree and three (3) to five (5) years of experience or seven (7) years of experience or any similar combination of   education and experience. </li><li> Certified Payroll Professional preferred. </li><li> Lawson experience preferred. </li><li> Executive pay and multi-location/state experience preferred.  </li></ul><p> </p><p  >  </p><p  >  </p><p  >  </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="105596" ncat="105" recordCount="848">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-08-01 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>13208</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Sr. Application Analyst (Lawson) ~ HR & Payroll]]></jobTitle>
    <department><![CDATA[It - Information Technology]]></department>
    <schedule>Full Time</schedule>
    <shift>1st - Day</shift>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=105596]]></url>
    <jobId>105596</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>srapplicationanalystlawsonhrpayroll105596</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p    >The overall responsibility of the <b>Sr. Application Analyst (Lawson) - HR & Payroll</b> is to provide client support, perform analysis, design, configuration, testing, documentation and roll out of technologies to meet Ardent's enterprise needs. Lead designated projects within the HR/Payroll environment. Additional  responsibilities include but are not limited to: developing system strategies with management and other stakeholders, conducting business needs analyses, identifying and mitigating project risks, supporting the application users and assisting in the implementation of the application projects.</p>  <p  ><b> Primary Duties and Responsibilities </b>    </p>  <p  ><b> Analysis and Solution Definition: </b>    </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  > Quickly      understands the business issues and data challenges of the organization      and industry.   </li>  <li  > Identifies the      organization's strengths and weaknesses and suggests areas of improvement.   </li>  <li  > Develops      functional requirements, specifications and system design specifications      for business requests.   </li>  <li  > Develops or      oversees the development of system documentation, user manuals and      training classes for application suite.   </li>  <li  > Sets Clear      Direction  tells others where you are going & how to get there and      why   </li>  <li  > Leads testing      efforts and ensures issues are identified, tracked, reported on and      resolved in a timely manner.   </li> </ul>  <p  >     </p>  <p  >     </p>  <p  ><b> Project Execution: </b>    </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  > Evaluates      current state processes and identifies gaps to future state process around      utilization of applications to maximize departmental and organizational      efficiency and effectiveness.   </li>  <li  > Communicates and      applies project standards.   </li>  <li  > Assists in      enforcement of project deadlines and schedules.   </li>  <li  > Takes input from      supervisor and appropriately and accurately applies comments/feedback.   </li>  <li  > Manages      resources in accordance with project schedule.   </li>  <li  > Consistently      delivers high-quality services to business stakeholders.   </li>  <li  > Understands the      components of running a fiscally successful project.   </li> </ul>  <p  >     </p>  <p  ><b> Communication: </b>    </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  > Assists in the      facilitation of team and client meetings.   </li>  <li  > Delivers      informative, well-organized presentations.   </li>  <li  > Understands how      to communicate difficult/sensitive information tactfully.   </li> </ul>  <p  >     </p>  <p  ><b> Problem Solving: </b>    </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  > Prioritizes and      resolves issues.   </li>  <li  > Provides ongoing      analysis, maintenance, and technical and functional support for      application systems throughout the organization.    </li>  <li  > Provides      leadership and technical guidance to identify system deficiencies and      analyze system problems and solutions.   </li>  <li  > Exhibits      confidence and an extensive knowledge of emerging industry practices when      solving business problems.   </li>  <li  > Collaborates      with business stakeholders to introduce innovative solutions.   </li>  <li  > Thinks and acts      for the benefit of the whole.   </li> </ul>  <p  >     </p>  <p  ><b> Leadership: </b>    </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  > Generates      enthusiasm among team members.   </li>  <li  > Proactively      seeks opportunities to serve in leadership roles.   </li>  <li  > Challenges      others to develop as leaders while serving as a role model.   </li>  <li  > Facilitates      effective team interaction.   </li>  <li  > Acknowledges and      appreciates each team member's contributions.   </li>  <li  > Develops and      fosters relationships with business stakeholders.   </li>  <li  > Continually      seeks opportunities to increase customer satisfaction.   </li>  <li  > Manages business      stakeholder expectations effectively.   </li>  <li  > Mentors those      with less experience through informal channels.   </li>  <li  > Leads internal      teams/task forces.   </li> </ul>  <p  >     </p>  <p  >     </p>  <p  ><b> General: </b>    </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  > Participates in      support on-call rotation.   </li>  <li  > Embodies and      Promotes Core Values:  Inquisitiveness, Team-Mindedness, Passionate,      and Positive Attitude.   </li>  <li  > A relentless      drive to be the best.   </li>  <li  > Ability to      travel as needed   </li>  <li  > Other duties as      assigned.   </li> </ul>  <p    >   </p>  <p  >     </p>  <p  ><b> Qualifications </b>    </p>  <p  >     </p>  <p  ><b> Education </b>    </p>  <p  > Bachelor's Degree, or equivalent business experience in supporting a Human Resource &/Payroll ERP system such as Lawson, PeopleSoft, SAP, JDEdwards.    </p>  <p  >     </p>  <p  ><b> Experience </b>    </p>  <ul type="disc">  <li  > 5-7      years  of experience in a HR Technology function or comparable role   </li>  <li  > Lawson      application certification a plus   </li>  <li  > Healthcare      experience preferred.   </li>  <li  > Technology      aptitude  and learning ability   </li>  <li  > Project      Management skills, knowledge and experience   </li>  <li  > Customer Service      oriented   </li>  <li  > High level of      accountability and ability to work independently   </li>  <li  > Flexible with      the ability to lead multiple projects and  prioritize tasks as      necessary   </li>  <li  > Strong      organization, customer service and time management skills   </li>  <li  > Excellent      communication skills, written and verbal   </li> </ul>  <p  >     </p>  <p  >   </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="108244" ncat="105" recordCount="849">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-06-30 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>16100</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Lead Application Analyst ~ MIDAS]]></jobTitle>
    <department><![CDATA[It - Information Technology]]></department>
    <schedule>Full Time</schedule>
    <shift>1st - Day</shift>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=108244]]></url>
    <jobId>108244</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>leadapplicationanalystmidas108244</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[    Ardent Health Services   invests in quality health care. In people, technology, facilities and communities, Ardent makes considerable investments, producing high quality care and extraordinary results.    <p><b> **This position has a work from home option or can be based in Nashville, TN.  </b></p><p> The overall responsibility of the <b>Lead Application Analyst, Quality Systems</b> is to provide functional support and implementation support of Quality and Analytics applications that enable the achievement of quality outcomes across the enterprise. These responsibilities include but are not limited to:  supporting application users and assisting in the implementation of quality and analytics  applications. This person will champion the overall implementation of standardized severity adjusted clinical outcomes reporting across the company,  a common reporting format and structure which are AHRQ requirements for PSO (Patient Safety Organization) certification.    </p>  Education  <p    ></p><ul><li> Bachelor's Degree, or equivalent business experience, required in clinical or healthcare industry. </li></ul><p> </p>  Experience  <p    ></p><ul><li> At least five years experience in clinical care or healthcare delivery with Midas+ application experience preferred. </li><li> Expertise in the use of a clinical application module as a super user or IT&S support analyst. </li><li> Proven ability to understand business and clinical issues and objectives as well as the ability to translate them into application solutions. </li><li> Exposure to application architecture, databases or system design. </li><li> Understands Internet, Intranet and client/server architectures. </li><li> Experience with leading clinical analytics initiatives. </li><li> Exposure to clinical quality solutions related to pharmacy, infection control, and risk events. </li><li> Exceptional  communication skills. </li><li> Demonstrated  experience with the following Midas+ Products: </li><ul><li> Care Manager </li><li> Seeker </li><li> Live </li><li> DataVision </li><li> Statit PPR </li><li> Statit piMD </li></ul></ul><p> </p><p  ><b> Primary Duties and Responsibilities:   </b></p>        Analysis and Solution Definition  <p    ></p><ul><li> Quickly understands the business issues and data challenges of the organization and industry. </li><li> Leads projects to develop and implement clinical quality analytics and reports. </li><li> Identifies the organization's strengths and weaknesses and suggests areas of improvement. </li><li> Develops or oversees the development of system documentation, user manuals and training classes for application suite. </li><li> Creates and maintains detailed test plans and scripts. </li><li> Participates in testing efforts and ensures issues are identified, tracked, reported on and resolved in a timely manner. </li></ul><p> </p><p    ><b  >Project Execution</b></p><p    ></p><ul><li> Leads complex projects with major impact to the enterprise. </li><li> Takes input from supervisor and appropriately and accurately applies comments/feedback. </li><li> Executes assigned project tasks in accordance with project schedule. </li><li> Consistently delivers high-quality services to business stakeholders. </li></ul><p> </p>        Communication  <p    ></p><ul><li> Assists with preparation of team and client meeting communications. </li></ul><p> </p>   Problem Solving   <p    ></p><ul><li> Prioritizes and resolves issues. </li><li> Provides ongoing analysis, maintenance, and technical and functional support for application systems throughout the organization.  </li><li> Provides input and guidance to identify system deficiencies and analyze system problems and solutions. </li><li> Strives to develop knowledge of emerging industry practices when solving business problems. </li><li> Supports the Team Leadership and overall IT&S Leadership in developing innovative solutions.  </li></ul><p> </p>         Leadership       <p    ></p><ul><li> Generates enthusiasm among team members. </li><li> Proactively seeks opportunities to expand knowledge. </li><li> Facilitates effective team interaction. </li><li> Acknowledges and appreciates each team Dmember's contributions. </li><li> Develops and fosters relationships with business stakeholders. </li><li> Continually seeks opportunities to increase customer satisfaction. </li><li> Collaborates with Team Leadership to manage business stakeholder expectations effectively. </li></ul><p> </p>         General       <p    ></p><ul><li> Participates in support on-call rotation. </li><li> Ability to travel up to 50%. </li><li> Other duties as assigned. </li></ul>  <p> </p><p    >                                                                          </p><p> </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="109405" ncat="105" recordCount="850">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-09-06 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>17381</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Application Analyst ~ Epic Resolute Hospital Billing]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=109405]]></url>
    <jobId>109405</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>applicationanalystepicresolutehospitalbilling109405</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p    >Ardent Health Services (AHS) is a national healthcare company headquartered in Nashville, TN.  Our subsidiaries own and operate hospitals and multispecialty physician practices in three states.  Ardent includes:  3 health systems with 14 hospitals, 2,194 licenses beds, 12,000 employees, and 3 physician groups with 270 employed physicians.  Within the industry, we are noted for recognizing that every hospital is as unique as the community it serves.  This in-depth understanding of how health care works at the local level is one of our great strengths.  </p><p    > We have an exciting opportunity to join our team as an <b>Application Analyst </b>in<b> Epic Resolute Hospital Billing.</b> </p><p    ><b>Position Summary:</b> <br><br>This position is responsible for in-depth knowledge of assigned Epic System software. This position conducts regular day-to-day communication, reviews software, demonstrates a deeper understanding of business operations, and works with Epic, the Project Team(s), Ardent Health Systems Subject Matter Experts, and end users to tailor the system to fit the organizations needs. This position routinely performs in-depth analysis of workflows, data collection, report details, and other technical issues associated with the use of Epic software; is responsible for developing and documenting the internal procedures that will be used in conjunction with Epic applications; and will design, build, test, install and maintain those solutions.   </p><p    ><b> </b></p><p    ><b>Job Responsibilities:</b>    </p><p    ></p><ul><li>              Work with Application Managers/Directors/etc. and the entire Project Team, to collect, analyze and document business operations and workflow. </li><li>              Complete all tasks in a timely manner with accurate documentation. </li><li>              Collaborate effectively with colleagues and across teams to achieve the completion of tasks. </li><li>              Troubleshoot problems and address questions from users, and provide on-call support on a rotating basis. </li><li>              Make recommendations, review and test changes, enhancements, and each new release as assigned. </li><li>              Ensure the test scripts have been created, reviewed, and updated to reflect proposed workflow solutions. </li><li>              Analyze data conversion needs. </li><li>              Support the training team by keeping trainers abreast of new functionality and system changes. </li><li>              Analyze new functionality in new releases to identify impact. </li><li>              Understands interface requirements and considerations to ensure appropriate testing is done to validate workflow from end to end. </li><li>              Provide assigned on-site support during go-lives and system upgrades. </li><li>              Ensures all quality assurance processes are followed, including change management and testing efforts. </li><li>              Actively participate and contribute in meetings. </li><li>              Works with the Application Manager/Director in the assessment of projects for scoping and timelines. </li><li>              Participate in disaster recovery measures. </li></ul><p> </p><p    ><b> </b></p><p    ><b>Minimum Qualifications:</b>    </p><p    ></p><ul><li>              Must have a BA/BS degree or equivalent and 2+ years of experience. </li><li>              Certified in Epic Resolute Hospital Billing </li><li>              Demonstrate effective oral, written communication and follow-up skills, as well as strong interpersonal relationship skills. </li><li>              Demonstrate strong desktop tool usage including Word, Excel, and PowerPoint. </li><li>              Must have good process design experience. </li><li>              Demonstrate basic project management skills (ability to lead meetings, prioritize, resolve conflicts, maintain issues list, manage project plan). </li><li>              Must be self-motivated, detail-oriented, and a problem solver. </li></ul><p> </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="108425" ncat="105" recordCount="855">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-07-14 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>16337</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Engineer ~ Citrix]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=108425]]></url>
    <jobId>108425</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>srsystemsengineercitrix108425</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<div> Ardent Health Services (AHS) is a national healthcare company headquartered in Nashville, TN.  Our subsidiaries own and operate hospitals and multispecialty physician practices in three states.  Ardent includes:  3 health systems with 14 hospitals, 2,194 licenses beds, 12,000 employees, and 3 physician groups with 270 employed physicians.  Within the industry, we are noted for recognizing that every hospital is as unique as the community it serves.  This in-depth understanding of how healthcare works at the local level is one of our great strengths.  </div><div>   </div><div> The <b>Intel Sr. Systems Engineer - Citrix </b>will be responsible for advanced level of securing, maintaining and monitoring the health of the server environment throughout the enterprise, which encompasses conducting utilization studies and the establishment of fault notification processes, analyzing data to recognize trends and create automated proactive measures to prevent application downtime.  Provides second and third level end-user support and mentor junior members of the Operations team. This position will work closely with other members of the Ardent Information Technology team to support the overall mission of the company and its long-term strategic business initiatives.  </div><div>   </div>  Education  <ul><li>  Required-degree in Information Technology / Computer Science or equivalent technical training.  </li><li>  Required-MCSE 2000/2003/2008 and/or VCP  </li></ul>  Experience  <p    ></p><ul><li>   	 Minimum of seven years experience in information technology, preferably in the healthcare industry  </li><li>   	   Minimum of five years experience working with Intel servers.  </li><li>   	   Minimum of three years experience working in VMware and Citrix environment.  </li><li>   	   Project management experience as it relates to user and server migration  </li><li>  	  Working knowledge and experience with ITIL foundation processes.  </li><li>  	  Experience with SolarWinds Orion monitoring.  </li><li>  	  Experience with Cisco UCS and IBM server platforms.  </li><li>  	  Extensive experience with securing a Microsoft server environment.  </li></ul><p>   </p>  Additional Requirements  <p> </p><p> </p><ul><li>Extensive knowledge of Citrix.</li><li> Extensive knowledge of Microsoft 2003, 2008, and 2012 Server. </li><li> Extensive knowledge of core infrastructure services (DNS, DHCP, IIS, AD group policies, Exchange, File Services, etc.) </li><li> Extensive knowledge supporting and administering enterprise applications such as VMware vCenter and ESXi, VDI solutions such as VMware View or XenDesktop, Rightfax services, Exchange services, Tivoli Endpoint Manager, and Citrix Presentation Server. </li><li> Extensive knowledge with clustering and highly available network solutions across multiple data centers. </li><li> Expert at troubleshooting complex problems. </li><li> Broad knowledge of systems management, scripting and automation. </li><li> B  road knowledge of storage solutions including SAN, NAS, CIFs, NFS, replication, deduplication. </li><li> Strong working knowledge of Scripting.    </li><li> Knowledge of applicable data privacy practices and laws (HIPAA). </li><li> Prior healthcare experience preferred. </li></ul><p> </p>  <p> <br> </p><p  ><b> Primary Duties and Responsibilities </b></p><p  ></p><ul><li>  Provide advanced level of support for servers, storage systems and infrastructure services. This individual may lead and direct the work of others on occasion to accomplish the common goals of the Operations team. This individual also participates in the planning and implementation of policies and procedures to ensure system provisioning and maintenance is consistent with company goals, industry best practices, and regulatory requirements.  </li><li>  Assist with the implementation of new technologies and verify that all procedural documentation is accurate, and that knowledge transfer from the engineering team is completed prior to any technology being placed in the Production environment.  </li><li>  Act as a contributor to enterprise level strategic projects, meeting milestone deadlines, and accomplishing project action items.  </li><li>  Ensure that proper operating procedures are adhered to during the full lifecycle of all servers throughout the enterprise including documentation, server builds, server maintenance, monitoring, support, refresh/upgrades, and decommission.  </li><li>  Required to administer data within corporate change, problem management and request systems; monitor assignment and completion of efforts documented in these systems; and properly escalate issues to management. Through escalations this role may serve as a point of contact for interactions with vendors on issue resolution.  </li><li>  Installs various types of software including operating systems and applications on a variety of hardware platforms including system updates, patches and configuration changes.  </li><li>  Analyze monitoring data to recognize trends and create proactive solutions to prevent recurring issues  </li><li>  Maintain operations of enterprise shared services and assist application teams as needed  </li><li>  Installs and maintains server hardware, system racks ensuring a visually clean and consistent environment. With installation and maintenance comes the need to maintain the asset inventory across the brand, including servers and software licenses.  </li><li>  Facilitate training, coaching, and mentoring junior team members to promote their skills development.  </li><li>  Serve as level 3 support of core infrastructure services utilizing the incident management ticketing system. Works closely with IT&S teams to resolve internal customer issues.  </li><li> Perform other duties as assigned.  </li></ul><p> <br> </p><div>   </div><div><div><b> Benefits </b></div><div>   </div><ul type="disc"  ><li    > Competitive Paid Time Off program<b>  </b> </li><li    > 401(k) Retirement Savings<b>  </b> </li><li    > Competitive Salary<b>  </b> </li><li    > Bonus targets based on company and individual performance<b>  </b> </li><li    > Comprehensive Medical, Dental and Vision Benefits<b>  </b> </li><li    > Company provided & Optional Life Insurance<b>  </b> </li><li    > Healthcare & dependant care flexible spending accounts </li></ul></div>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="107700" ncat="105" recordCount="888">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-06-01 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>15554</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[Underpayment Specialist]]></jobTitle>
    <department><![CDATA[Revenue Integrity]]></department>
    <schedule>Full Time</schedule>
    <shift>1st - Day</shift>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=107700]]></url>
    <jobId>107700</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>underpaymentspecialist107700</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[   Ardent Health Services invests in quality health care. In people, technology, facilities and communities, Ardent makes considerable investments, producing high quality care and extraordinary results   <p> We are seeking a detail oriented Insurance Underpayment Recovery Specialist with an outstanding work ethic and sharp analytical skills to join our team.      If you have a firm understanding of Payor Contracts and Hospital Reimbursement then this is the perfect opportunity for you.    </p>  <p  >     </p>  <p    ><b><i><u> PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES </u></i></b></p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 1.        <!--[endif]-->Identify and resolve issues associated with claim underpayment.   </p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 2.        <!--[endif]-->Contact designated insurance carriers to inquire on underpayment.   </p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 3.        <!--[endif]-->Send appeal letters to insurance carriers.   </p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 4.        <!--[endif]-->Perform follow up with payors.   </p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 5.        <!--[endif]-->Research contracts and escalate contract issues.   </p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 6.        <!--[endif]-->Review Managed Care Contracts and compare against claims to identify discrepancies.   </p>  <p    ><b><i>   </i></b></p>  <p    ><b><i> Note:  The essential job functions of this position are not limited to the duties listed above. </i></b></p><p    >   </p><p    ><b><i><u>  KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS, AND ABILITIES </u></i></b></p>  <p  > 1.       Maintain working knowledge of contract management and patient accounting systems </p>  <p  ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 2.     Build relationships with facility Finance, Business office and Managed Care Personnel   </p>  <p  ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 3.     <!--[endif]-->Ability to analyze data to determine corrective actions needed to effectively understand changes required to effectively appeal underpaid amounts   </p>  <p  ><!--[if !supportLists]--> 4.     Ability to understand payment methodology and guide underpayment recovery specialists to identify and collect underpayments from contracted commercial and governmental payors.   </p>    <i>QUALIFICATIONS</i>    <p    ><b><i> Education:     </i></b></p>  <p    > High School Diploma.  Degree preferred<b><i>  </i></b> </p>  <p    > <b><i>Experience:</i></b>   </p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]-->      <!--[endif]-->2+ years experience in insurance collections or underpayment recovery </p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]-->      <!--[endif]-->Understanding of Reimbursement and Hospital Contracts </p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]-->      <!--[endif]-->Detail Oriented Analytical Thinker </p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]-->      <!--[endif]-->Excellent verbal and phone communication skills </p>  <p    ><!--[if !supportLists]-->      <!--[endif]-->Proficient in Microsoft Office </p>  <p    > </p><p    ><b  ><i>Additional Requirements: </i></b> Excellent verbal, analytical and interpersonal skills.  </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="107477" ncat="103" recordCount="896">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-05-18 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>15290</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[VP, Human Resources]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=107477]]></url>
    <jobId>107477</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>No</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Lovelace Health System Division</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Albuquerque</facility_city>
    <facility_state>NM</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100020</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>vphumanresources107477</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p  >We are currently recruiting for a <b>Vice President of Human Resources</b> for Lovelace Health System (LHS) in Albuquerque, NM.  Lovelace Health System consists of 6 hospitals, a medical group, 3,700 employees, 606 licensed beds, and $351 million in capital improvements since 2001. Lovelace Health System is owned by  <b> Ardent </b>    Health Services, a nationwide provider of hospital and healthcare services which <b> </b> owns and operates 14 hospitals serving three major markets.   </p>  <p  >   </p>  <p  >The <b>Vice President of Human Resources</b> (VP HR) reports directly to the system CEO and oversees all aspects of Human Resources for LHS.  This position is a key promoter of strategic priorities which include Quality, People, Service, Growth and Financial with an emphasis on People.  Our goal for the strategic priority of People is to attract, engage, develop and retain high performing talent and to achieve LHS's mission.  The VP of HR fosters an environment of effective relationships and performance excellence.  </p>  <p  >   </p>  <p  >Key indicators include:</p>  <p  >-Integrity                                                                         -Mentoring</p>  <p  >-Accountability                                                               -Recognition</p>  <p  >-Others needs above own                                           -Professional development</p>  <p  >-Mutual respect                                                             -Solicit & act upon feedback</p>  <p  >-Conflict resolution</p>  <p  >   </p>  <p  >The VP of HR will guide and maintain functional relationships at all levels of HR staff within the organization and will have direct oversight over all of human resources including Organizational Development, Shared Services and the LHS Resource Team. Additionally, this position will have a direct focus on strategic planning and the deployment of strategic initiatives.</p>  <p  >Examples of Responsibilities:  </p>  <p  >-Engage executives to understand talent needs of the businesses and define responses </p>  <p  >-Ensure effective use & implementation of enterprise-wide HR & Talent initiatives </p>  <p  >-Promote and foster a healthy work environment</p>  <p  >-Uphold all compliance standards, including OFCCP, DNV, CMS, Department of Labor, HR policies and </p>  <p  >   other regulatory requirements</p>  <p  >-Build, develop and lead a team of HR professionals within LHS</p>  <p  >-Drive effective leader and employee communications initiatives </p>  <p  >-Ensure operational excellence, monitoring, and measuring the effectiveness and efficiency of the HR </p>  <p  >  leaders and teams</p>  <p  >-Identify and facilitate use of HR service contractors as needed</p>  <p  >-Set consistent compensation practices within LHS</p><p  > </p><p  ><b>Job Requirements:</b></p>  <p  >Experience:</p>  <p  >   </p>  <p  >-Five+ (5+) years HR experience as the lead HR executive reporting to a system or regional CEO in a work </p>  <p  >  environment reflective of the scope & complexity of the Lovelace Health System </p>  <p  >-Other preferred experience profile could included multiple years as a lead HR executive with regional or </p>  <p  >  national accountability in a healthcare service related organization. </p>  <p  >-Bachelors degree in Human Resources Management or related field.  Masters degree preferred</p>  <p  >-PHR or SPHR certification preferred</p>  <p  >    </p>  <p  >   </p>  <p  >   </p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Corporate</jobNcat>
  </job>
  <job id="108814" ncat="103" recordCount="897">
    <datePosted><![CDATA[
            2016-08-05 00:00:00 
          ]]></datePosted>
    <reqNum>16740</reqNum>
    <jobTitle><![CDATA[VP, Physician Operations]]></jobTitle>
    <department/>
    <schedule/>
    <shift/>
    <hours/>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.healthcaresource.com/bsahs/index.cfm?fuseaction=search.jobDetails&template=dsp_job_details.cfm&cJobId=108814]]></url>
    <jobId>108814</jobId>
    <jobApplicationType>external</jobApplicationType>
    <Executive>Yes</Executive>
    <Corporate>Yes</Corporate>
    <facility_name>Ardent Health Services</facility_name>
    <facility_city>Nashville</facility_city>
    <facility_state>TN</facility_state>
    <facilityId>100019</facilityId>
    <new_url_title>vpphysicianoperations108814</new_url_title>
    <jobDescription><![CDATA[<p>Are you looking to join a stable and growing company where you can truly make an impact? Are you a visionary who is inspired by a challenge and will put forth the effort to make it successful? If so, then this is the job and company for you! </p>  <p> </p>  <p>We are seeking a true, dynamic leader that understands the importance of developing positive relationships and trust with our 360+ physicians and leadership teams and how to maintain that dynamic within the organization. Someone that can bring their expertise to the business to help create strategies to enhance and grow physician services throughout the organization through creative initiatives. Someone that can develop a plan to better align with independent physicians within all markets.  A true leader that can be consulted when it comes to strategies of how to align and integrate the physician practices within the organization while maintaining positive working relationships! </p>  <p> </p>  <p>Working at Ardent means changing lives!  We know the work we do and the support we give has a direct impact on the happiness of our teams and the consistency, and quality of care our patients receive. We understand that what makes a job exceptional are the relationships you have with the people you work with!   This position works closely with the division and physician group leadership in our markets to identify opportunities to enhance the practices.  We are looking for someone to coach and motivate teams in both physician groups at the corporate and local levels by collecting data and communicating information in order to maintain the best possible relationships within the organization and throughout the communities we serve. </p><p> </p><p>If creating an impact in a growing company while ensuring a healthy work environment through creative initiatives is something you are interested in, then you have found the right place!  </p>      <p> </p>  <p>PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES </p>  <ul><li>To help establish new strategies, opportunities, and options to enhance physician     practices throughout the company.  </li><li>Identify and disseminate "best practices" throughout physician practices by working with Division and Corporate operations.  </li><li>Develop and monitor methodologies to evaluate the financial performance and benchmarking of the employed clinical practices.  </li><li>Create standardization across all markets surrounding our EPIC implmentation  </li><li>Identify methodologies to reduce the overall investment in the physician practices (e.g. enhance productivity, improve access, evaluate new models of care, etc.).  </li><li>Assist in the development of quality metrics and benchmarks for all specialists and non-physician practitioners to ensure the provision of safe, high quality care.  </li></ul>          <ul><li>Assist market leaders in developing company-wide strategy to maximize performance under value-based reimbursement programs. </li></ul>  <p> </p>  <p>Education: Bachelors degree in related field required.  MBA, MHA, or other related Master's Degree preferred. </p>  <p> </p>  <p>Experience: A minimum of seven (7) years experience in healthcare administration. </p>  <p> </p>  <p>Additional Requirements: </p>  <p>             Background in finance preferred. </p>  <p>             Experience in leading Physician Practices preferably healthcare system physician group practices and experience in physician practice support operations.<b> </b></p>]]></jobDescription>
    <jobNcat>Executive</jobNcat>
  </job>
</jobSearch>
